



514-230-618



przemyslawleksa@gmail.com



przemyslawleksa.heroku app.com



linkedin.com/in/pleksa



github.com/przemekleksa

ABOUT ME

For many years I have been creating web pages for friends, acquaintances and small companies. I finished computer science studies with specialization in internet technologies with great scores. Lately I finished a Fullstack Developer Bootcamp. I would like to increase my web development skills by working with people that have more experience and knowledge than me.

LANGUAGES

English C2

INTERESTS

Tarantino movies Motor sports First person shooter games

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych również na potrzeby przyszłych rekrutacji, zgodnie z art. 6 ust lit. a Rozporządzenia Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osob fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (ogólne rozporządzenie o ochronie danych)

l agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of

natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)

PRZEMYSŁAW LEKSA

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER Freelancer

2016 - present

Creating websites in HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Bootstrap, jQuery. Setting up and modifying Wordpress and Prestashop pages.

Using GIMP and Photoshop to create website layouts.

ORDER MANAGEMENT COORDINATOR al.to (x-kom group)

April 2019 - present

Ordering products. Confirming clients orders. Close cooperation with product managers, chief executive officer, copywriters, contact center, warehouse staff and suppliers

SENIOR COPYWRITER al.to (x-kom group)

June 2016 - March 2019

Creating product presentation for online shop and auctions. Preparing product specifications. Training new employees. Setting up and management of department wiki help page. Highest employee evaluation score in whole department that employs 15 people.

PROJECT MANAGER Pink Parrot Media

November 2015 - January 2016

Acquiring clients preferences and needs. Managing a team of developers. CMS systems support. Creating Content. Editing websites

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE

October 2012 - December 2016

Wyższa Szkoła Zarządzania i Bankowości w Krakowie Specialization: Internet technologies

COURSES

CODEBRAINERS

March 2019 - June 2019

Fullstack Developer Bootcamp (328 hours of python, JS, SQL, React, Redux Django)

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Javascript, React, Redux, jQuery, RWD, Python, Django, Flask, PHP, GIMP, npm, gulp, Photoshop, Wordpress, Prestashop

VOLUNTEERING

POLISH GROUP LEADER Erasmus+ Hungary

2014 & 2015

Participation in daily meetings with other countries leaders. Taking care of participants needs. Creating a friendly environment. Participation in analog photography and bike building workshops.